{
    "subject": "resource/Harald_Wohlrapp",
    "predicate": "property/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Hildesheim",
    "human_readable": "Harald Wohlrapp was born in Hildesheim.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9773338437080383,
            "question": "Where did Harald Wohlrapp live after he was born in Hildesheim?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9278594851493835,
            "question": "Where was Harald Wohlrapp born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7642847895622253,
            "question": "What might have influenced Harald Wohlrapp growing up in Hildesheim?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5536462068557739,
            "question": "What are some potential connections between Harald Wohlrapp and his birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4076767563819885,
            "question": "What is known about Harald Wohlrapp's early life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4019702672958374,
            "question": "Are there any famous people from Hildesheim?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3556996285915375,
            "question": "Can you tell me anything about Harald Wohlrapp's family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32239553332328796,
            "question": "Is there anything notable about the city of Hildesheim?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3113809823989868,
            "question": "Has Harald Wohlrapp made any significant contributions to society?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30073845386505127,
            "question": "What is Harald Wohlrapp's profession or area of expertise?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Harald Wohlrapp was born in Hildesheim.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2997_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Harald Wohlrapp made any significant contributions to society?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2997_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there anything notable about the city of Hildesheim?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2997_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me anything about Harald Wohlrapp's family?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2997_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2997_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2997_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2997_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2997_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2997_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2997_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2997_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2997_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2997_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2997_4.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here's my evaluation:\n\n* The triple \"Harald Wohlrapp was born in Hildesheim\" is supported by the documents. In fact, there are multiple mentions of Harald Wohlrapp being born in Hildesheim, specifically: \"Harald Wohlrapp was born on June 6, 1944, in Hildesheim, Lower Saxony, Germany.\"\n\nTherefore, my response to this query is:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nLet me know if you'd like me to evaluate any other triples!"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents state that Harald R. Wohlrapp was born on June 6, 1944, in Hildesheim, Lower Saxony, Germany, which supports the triple \"Harald Wohlrapp was born in Hildesheim.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}